Evan Parker

London, United Kingdom • evancp@hotmail.com • www.evanparker.co.uk

https://www.linkedin.com/in/evan-parker-9a336987/ • https://www.instagram.com/evsparks87/

Profile

I am a creative individual, who is passionate about technology, all things digital, and cultural experiences. I have broad experience in the museum and culture sectors, specifically with arts/project management, and more recent experience with web/app development as a freelance developer.

08/2021 - 10/2021

05/2021 - 07/2021

Professional Experience	
09/2022 - present	 Digital Product Assistant, Royal Academy of Arts Supporting the Data, Product & Infrastructure team with product support, Working with Software Engineers to test code and the RA website, quality assurance and logging tickets Administration Organising sprints
06/2022 — present	 Freelance Web Developer, Atom Design Worked with a web designer to build out small e-commerce websites on a page by page basis with HTML, CSS and Javascript Converted Figma designs to accurate code Gave feedback on the feasibility of designs and sought solutions to problems Learned new technology stacks to work more closely with the organisation's preferred ways of working
09/2017 — present	 Cultural Events Assistant, British Library Assisted with the delivery, planning and administration of the Library's Cultural Events programme Worked with the web development team to build an event archive, showcasing years of Cultural Event archive material Took on Web Officer duties to regularly update and develop content for the Library website with a CMS
02/2015 - present	Barbican Host, Barbican Centre Worked on busy classical music, theatre and exhibitions.
Education	
09/2006 – 02/2010	Creative Writing, University of East London 2:1
09/2004 - 05/2006	Media Studies, Sports Studies, English Literature, <i>Graveney Sixth Form</i> Media- B, English- B, Sports Studies- C
09/1999 – 05/2004	Graveney School 6 A's 9 (including IT, English and Science) and 4 C's
Courses	
05/2022 - 05/2022	Python for Librarians, Juice Academy
03/2022 - 05/2022	Full Stack Developer 2022, Udemy
12/2021 - 02/2022	Intermediate JavaScript Nanodegree, Udacity

React Nanodegree, Udacity

Front-end Development, General Assembly

Skills

Administration, Project Management, Customer Service, Copywriting, React JS, JavaScript, Python, Node JS/Express, HTML, CSS, MongoDB, SQL, Sass, Bootstrap, Jest